Recreational Services and Athletics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Intercollegiate athletic records, 1965 - 1991; F-80-5; 1 m of textual records
  - Soccer records, 1969 - 1991; F-80-5-4; 11 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the operation of the men's and women's intercollegiate soccer program. Activities and topics documented include the early history of the team as a recreational club; the recording of team statistics and records; travel, liaison with the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics and member universities; and relations with the North American Soccer League. Predominant document types include correspondence, rosters, schedules, travel itineraries, statistics, press clippings, news releases, programs (game and season), press guides, and newsletters.
    Records related to the operation of the intercollegiate soccer program may also be found in the following series: Recreational Club Records; Schedules; Workshop and Course Records; Publication and Publicity Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
    - [Soccer club/team schedules and general information: collected file], 1969 - 1980; F-80-5-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Soccer, 1975; F-80-5-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Soccer, 1975 - 1980; F-80-5-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Soccer, 1976 - 1979; F-80-5-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - [Soccer statistics and publicity: collected file], 1977 - 1980; F-80-5-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Soccer, 1980 - 1981; F-80-5-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Soccer, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Diachem Bowl, 1987 - 1988; F-80-5-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Men's soccer, 1988; F-80-5-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Men's soccer, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Women's soccer, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
  - Swimming and diving records, 1965 - 1991; F-80-5-5; 5 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the operation of the men's and women's swimming and diving program. Activities and topics documented include the recording of swim meet results and records; travel; and liaison with the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics and member universities. Predominant document types include correspondence, rosters, schedules, travel itineraries, statistics, press clippings, news releases, programs (meet and season), and newsletters.
    Records related to the intercollegiate swimming and diving program may also be found in the following series: Schedules; Publication and Publicity Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
    - Swimming, 1965 - 1966; F-80-5-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Swimming, 1967 - 1975; F-80-5-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-9)
    - Swimming, 1976 - 1977; F-80-5-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Swimming and diving, 1980 - 1981; F-80-5-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Swimming and diving, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Swimming, 1988 - 1990; F-80-5-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Swimming, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
  - Track field records, 1968 - 1989; F-80-5-6; 4 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the operation of the men's and women's intercollegiate track and field program. Activities and topics documented include the recording of track and field meet results and records; travel; and liaison with the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics and member universities. Predominant document types include correspondence, rosters, schedules, travel itineraries, statistics, press clippings, news releases, and programs (meet and season).
    Records related to the intercollegiate track and field program may also be found in the following series: Schedules; Publication and Publicity Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
    - Track, 1968 - 1976; F-80-5-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Track and field, 1976 - 1977; F-80-5-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Women's track and field, 1976 - 1977; F-80-5-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Track and field, 1980 - 1981; F-80-5-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Track and field, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Track and field, 1988 - 1989; F-80-5-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
  - Other intercollegiate sports records, 1968 - 1991; F-80-5-7; 15 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the operation of the field hockey, golf, hockey, lacrosse, parachuting, rowing, skiing, volleyball, and wrestling teams. Activities and topics documented include the recording of team statistics and records; travel; and liaison with the National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics and member universities. Predominant document types include correspondence, rosters, schedules, travel itineraries, statistics, press clippings, news releases, and programs (game/meet and season).
    Records related to intercollegiate sports may also be found in the following series: Schedules; Publication and Publicity Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
    - Field hockey, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Field hockey, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Golf, 1972 - 1973; F-80-5-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Golf, 1977 - 1978; F-80-5-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Golf, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Golf, 1989 - 1990; F-80-5-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Golf, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Hockey, 1968 - 1973; F-80-5-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Lacrosse, 1979 - 1980; F-80-5-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - [Parachuting], 1975 - 1976; F-80-5-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Rowing (crew), 1974; F-80-5-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-10)
    - Women's rowing, 1980; F-80-5-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Rowing, 1982 - 1983; F-80-5-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - [Brief in Support of a Ski-Racing Team at Simon Fraser], 1969; F-80-5-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Ski team, 1982 - 1987; F-80-5-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Skiing, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Skiing alpine, 1988 - 1990; F-80-5-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Volleyball, 1973 - 1975; F-80-5-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Volleyball, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Women's volleyball, 1976 - 1977; F-80-5-7-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Volleyball, 1988 - 1990; F-80-5-7-0-21 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Volleyball, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-7-0-22 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1971 - 1975; F-80-5-7-0-23 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1976 - 1977; F-80-5-7-0-24 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1980 - 1981; F-80-5-7-0-25 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1982 - 1984; F-80-5-7-0-26 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1988 - 1990; F-80-5-7-0-27 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Wrestling, 1990 - 1991; F-80-5-7-0-28 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
  - Athletic awards and honours records, 1965 - 1989; F-80-5-8; 16 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records related to the granting of athletic awards and honours. Activities and topics documented include the establishment of athletic awards and guidelines for their disbursement; budgetary allocations; athlete of the month/year honours; and the annual Awards Banquet and the Sports Hall of Fame Banquet. Predominant document types include correspondence, Board of Governors reports, award application forms, award disbursement guidelines, budget material, photographs, player profiles, banquet agendas and programs, invitation lists, lists of award winners; receipts, news releases, and newsletters.
    Records related to athletic awards and honours may also be found in the following subseries: Sports information Office Files - General.
    - [Board of Governors Reports], 1965; F-80-5-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Simon Fraser University News Bulletins, 1966; F-80-5-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - [Athletic awards policies and related material: collected file], 1969 - 1970; F-80-5-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - [Athletic awards budget and related material], 1976 - 1978; F-80-5-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Athletics: athlete of the month/year, 1978 - 1979; F-80-5-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Ninth Annual Awards Banquet (program), 1974; F-80-5-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Athletics: athlete award winners and Athletic Banquet, 1974 - 1980; F-80-5-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Athletic Banquet award winners, 1982; F-80-5-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - Banquet papers, 1985; F-80-5-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-11)
    - 21st Annual Awards Banquet, 1986; F-80-5-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - 22nd Annual Awards Banquet, 1987; F-80-5-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - Athletic Awards Banquet, 1988; F-80-5-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - 23rd Annual Awards Banquet, 1988; F-80-5-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - 24th Annual Awards Banquet, 1989; F-80-5-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - 1st Annual SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1986; F-80-5-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - 1st Annual SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1986; F-80-5-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1987; F-80-5-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1988; F-80-5-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1988; F-80-5-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - SFU Sports Hall of Fame Banquet, 1989; F-80-5-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
    - Athletic Awards Banquet, 1967 - 1968; F-80-5-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
- Recreational club records, 1966 - 1989; F-80-6; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the operations of recreational clubs. Activities and topics documented include the establishment of general club guidelines; objectives of the Athletic Clubs Council; and operations of the cricket, rugby, sailing, skiing, and soccer clubs. Predominant document types include correspondence, handbooks, statements of objectives, minutes, press clippings, rosters, schedules, club histories and statistics, photographs, news bulletins, rule books, and reports.
  Records related to the soccer club may also be found in the following subseries: Soccer Records.
  - Recreational Club Program, 1968 - 1969; F-80-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
  - Clubs, 1968 - 1970; F-80-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-12)
  - [Cricket club: collected file], 1966 - 1971; F-80-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Minutes of cricket club general meetings: collected file], 1971; F-80-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Rugby football club correspondence: collected file], 1966 - 1977; F-80-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Rugby football club bulletins, minutes, and schedules: collected file], 1967 - 1968; F-80-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Minutes of the Vancouver Rugby Union: collected file], 1967 - 1968; F-80-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Rugby football club rules and regulations: collected file], 1967 - 1977; F-80-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Rugby football club photographs: collected file], 1974; F-80-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Rugby football club reports: collected file], 1982 - 1984; F-80-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - SFU sailing club, 1988 - 1989; F-80-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Ski club - incorporation, minutes, and correspondence: collected file], 1968 - 1970; F-80-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Soccer club constitution, agendas, and minutes: collected file], 1966; F-80-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Soccer club reports and correspondence: collected file], 1967 - 1974; F-80-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Soccer club photographs: collected file], [ca 1970] - [ca 1979]; F-80-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Tennis, 1975; F-80-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
- Schedules, 1972 - 1994; F-80-7; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of team schedules for both the intercollegiate athletic and recreation programs. Information recorded on the schedules include date of games/meets, opponents, host cities, and start times.
  Schedules may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
  - [Football], 1972; F-80-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Women's swimming, 1972; F-80-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Women's field hockey, 1975; F-80-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Soccer], 1977; F-80-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Women's flag football league, 1977; F-80-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Basketball], 1978 - 1979; F-80-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Team schedules], 1974 - 1976; F-80-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Athletics: schedules], 1980 - 1981; F-80-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Team schedules, 1982; F-80-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - [Team schedules], 1990 - 1994; F-80-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Athletic event masters, 1973 - 1976; F-80-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Athletic event masters, 1976 - 1978; F-80-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Athletic event masters, 1987 - 1988; F-80-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
- Workshop and course records, 1966 - 1992; F-80-8; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to the operation of both athletic and recreation workshops and courses. Activities and topics documented include sports clinics; the establishment of a coaching specialist program; government fitness and training centres; the Task Force on Active Health Sciences and Leisure Studies; general education activity classes; the establishment of athletic credit courses; and sports camps and summer programs. Predominant document types include correspondence, clinic notes and handouts, reports, program postings, financial statements and recommendations, program rationales, course proposal forms, and course descriptions.
  Records related to workshops and courses may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; and Publication and Publicity Records.
  - Coaching Specialist Program, 1968 - 1977; F-80-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Fall Workshops, 1970; F-80-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-13)
  - Coaching Specialist Program, 1971 - 1977; F-80-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - SFU Football Tribune and off season athletic program, 1966 - 1971; F-80-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - 3rd annual basketball clinic, 1967; F-80-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - 2nd annual football clinic, 1967; F-80-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - 3rd annual football clinic, 1968; F-80-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - General education activity classes, 1972 - 1977; F-80-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - [Coaching Specialist Program], 1974 - 1975; F-80-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - [Coaching and Sports Management course outline], 1975; F-80-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Volleyball Instructors Course, 1976; F-80-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Student Trainer Program, 1978; F-80-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Task Force on Active Health Sciences and Leisure Studies [and Coaching Specialist Program], 1979; F-80-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - [Sports camps and summer programs (postings)], 1983 - 1992; F-80-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Athletics credit courses, 1984 - 1986; F-80-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Sports camps [budgets and reports], 1986 - 1989; F-80-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Sports camps/mini university, 1987 - 1988; F-80-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - [Recreation fitness program], 1987 - 1989; F-80-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Sports camps/mini university, 1989; F-80-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - Sports camps - summer, 1990; F-80-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
- Publication and publicity records, 1960 - 1995; F-80-9; 81 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records related to publications and publicity produced by the Departments of Athletics and Recreation. Activities and topics documented include the promotion of team events and achievements; and the advertising of workshop/course offerings and other departmental services. The predominant document types include news releases, sports publications and newsletters, press clippings, press guides, programs (game/event and season), posters, and yearbooks.
  Files within the series annotated, collected file, indicate an artifical grouping created by a former archivist. Records within these files may have been collected from sources outside the fonds.
  Records related to publications and publicity may also be found in the following series: Intercollegiate Athletic Records; Workshop and Course Records; and Sports Information Office Files.
  Access to certain files containing personal information has been restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - News releases, 1974 - 1975; F-80-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 80-14)
  - [News releases], 1980 - 1983; F-80-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1982; F-80-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1983; F-80-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1984; F-80-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases], 1984 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - News releases, 1984 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1985; F-80-9-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases], 1985 - 1986; F-80-9-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - New releases, 1985 - 1986; F-80-9-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 80-15)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1986; F-80-9-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - News releases, 1986 - 1987; F-80-9-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases], 1986 - 1987; F-80-9-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - News releases, 1987; F-80-9-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1987; F-80-9-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases], 1987 - 1988; F-80-9-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1988; F-80-9-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1989; F-80-9-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1990; F-80-9-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 80-16)
  - [News releases], 1990; F-80-9-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [News releases: collected file], 1991; F-80-9-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
    Textual records; Graphic materials
  - [News releases], 1991; F-80-9-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [News releases], 1992; F-80-9-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Clansmen Chatter], 1973 - 1975; F-80-9-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - Pepsi Junior Clan Club [Newsletters], 1983 - 1984; F-80-9-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - Clan Club Newsletters [and related material], 1983 - 1987; F-80-9-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [SFU Update], 1982 - 1983; F-80-9-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - SFU Sport-O-Grams, 1973 - 1976; F-80-9-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - SFU Sport-O-Grams, 1981 - 1982; F-80-9-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Clansmen press clippings], 1973; F-80-9-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Simon Fraser University Basketball Newsletters], 1966 - 1989; F-80-9-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Simon Fraser University Basketball Newsletters], 1975; F-80-9-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - Basketball press guide, 1975 - 1976; F-80-9-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Basketball season programs], 1966 - 1978; F-80-9-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 80-17)
  - [Basketball season programs], 1980 - 1993; F-80-9-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Basketball game program], 1975; F-80-9-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football team composite photographs], 1965 - 1971; F-80-9-0-0-37 (Shelf Map cabinet)
  - [Football press books], 1966 - 1970; F-80-9-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - SFU Football Tribune, 1966 - 1972; F-80-9-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football programs and related material], 1967 - 1989; F-80-9-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football game programs], 1967 - 1992; F-80-9-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football for Fans (information booklet)], [ca 1960] - [ca 1969]; F-80-9-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - Working papers to print program 1970 UBC-SFU football game, F-80-9-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football press guide], 1975; F-80-9-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - Shrum Bowl programs, 1978 - 1979; F-80-9-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football] press kit, 1979; F-80-9-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Football season program], 1991; F-80-9-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 80-18)
  - [Soccer club/team press clippings: collected file], 1967 - 1978; F-80-9-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - Soccer press guides, 1978 - 1979; F-80-9-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Soccer season programs], 1986 - 1992; F-80-9-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [SFU: Watersport], 1966 - 1968; F-80-9-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Swimming and diving championships program], 1982; F-80-9-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Wrestling season program], 1988 - 1989; F-80-9-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Physical Development Centre], 1965; F-80-9-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Coaching Skills: Special Emphasis], [ca 1960] - [ca 1969]; F-80-9-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [The Student Athlete at Simon Fraser University (information booklets)], [ca 1960] - [ca 1969]; F-80-9-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser University Athletics (programs)], 1970 - 1971; F-80-9-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - Public relations, 1972 - 1973; F-80-9-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - Public relations, 1973 - 1974; F-80-9-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser Clan Sports Calendar], 1978 - 1979; F-80-9-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser University: Women's Athletics], 1979; F-80-9-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser University Student-Athlete Handbooks], 1982 - 1985; F-80-9-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Join Our Team (Clan Club)], 1989; F-80-9-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 80-19)
  - [Simon Fraser University Athletic Drug Information Booklet], [ca 1980] - [ca 1989]; F-80-9-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 80-19)